[
     {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [33, 33, 33, 33, 31, 36, 32, 35, 34]?",
      "correctAnswer": "33",
      "options": [
        "32",
        "33",
        "34",
        "35"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [37, 37, 33, 37, 32, 37, 35, 34, 36, 37]?",
      "correctAnswer": "37",
      "options": [
        "36",
        "37",
        "38",
        "39"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [37, 38, 34, 34, 35, 36, 33, 34]?",
      "correctAnswer": "34",
      "options": [
        "33",
        "34",
        "35",
        "36"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [38, 37, 39, 36, 35, 39, 39, 39, 34]?",
      "correctAnswer": "39",
      "options": [
        "38",
        "39",
        "40",
        "41"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [38, 35, 36, 40, 37, 40, 40, 40, 40, 39]?",
      "correctAnswer": "40",
      "options": [
        "39",
        "40",
        "41",
        "42"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [39, 38, 40, 40, 37, 41, 36, 40]?",
      "correctAnswer": "40",
      "options": [
        "39",
        "40",
        "41",
        "42"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [40, 38, 38, 38, 38, 42, 37, 39, 41]?",
      "correctAnswer": "38",
      "options": [
        "37",
        "38",
        "39",
        "40"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [40, 40, 41, 39, 43, 42, 38, 40, 40, 40]?",
      "correctAnswer": "40",
      "options": [
        "39",
        "40",
        "41",
        "42"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [44, 43, 44, 39, 44, 42, 41, 40]?",
      "correctAnswer": "44",
      "options": [
        "43",
        "44",
        "45",
        "46"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [43, 43, 46, 42, 40, 44, 43, 41, 43, 45]?",
      "correctAnswer": "43",
      "options": [
        "42",
        "43",
        "44",
        "45"
      ]
    }
]